Guide to the Willie Varela Papers, ca. 1960-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Accession 97-010
  - Four videos: 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - A Fragmented life
    - Broken line
    - A Series of observations
  - A lost man 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Four videos: (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Good Friday 1992-1993
    - Thanksgiving Day 1992-1993
    - Juarez Diary 1993
    - Rose phone rain 1993
  - Four videos: (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Video light, in my backyard 1993
    - Arid musings 1994
    - The bad girl 1994
    - Raw notes February 1995
  - The bad girl 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Speaking for myself 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Raw notes 1995 (Box 11, Folder 7)